They won again.
Team Sakamoto's amazing.
Nice job, Sakamoto.
I heard you beat the top French team!
I've never seen him in person before.
Could I be on your team, even just as a reserve?
He's really popular.
Well, of course he is.
He's the top-ranked player in Japan.
He's even been featured in gaming magazines.
Waiting for someone?
Huh?
Are you waiting for someone?
No...
I mean, I'm waiting for a friend.
They aren't here yet.
Then, want to play with us until they get here?
One of my team logged out, you see.
Oh, I couldn't.
I'm no good at this game.
I'd just slow you down.
I'll back you up.
Why are you hitting on her?
There aren't any girls on the internet, man.
Shut up, you two.
BTOOOM! is more fun
to play than to watch,
right?
O-Okay.
This was how I met Sakamoto.
It was a fateful encounter.
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
This is where tomorrow brings a new game
It's time to learn that pain is gain
Ready fight
To squash my past despair
kako no shitsubou nuritsubusu tame ni
I've had to sacrifice my future
gisei ni shite kita mirai
Until my life expires
boku no life ga tsukiru made
I'll keep fighting my fate
sono sadame buchikowashiteiku no sa
Ah, break out and start a revolution
Searching for the exact answer
hitotsu no kotae wo sagashite
I challenge myself to an extreme race
genkai no race ni idonde
I know it's my only chance
ichidokiri no chansu to shitte
I'll overcome my preordained fate
seotta unmei koeteikun da yo
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
the game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
Jeez Miho, why didn't you come yesterday?
I'm sorry, Himiko!
One of my brother's friends came over.
They hogged the game console.
Couldn't you at least have sent me a text?
They made me play with them.
You know you'll be paying for the snacks now, right?
I know that!
You really do stand out, Himiko.
Honestly, I hate that.
Got it rough, huh?
Then give it all to me.
Your hair, eye color, and your boobs!
You can have them!
Oh, so yesterday...
I played BTOOOM! with Sakamoto.
Sakamoto?
The best player in Japan.
Just three games with his team
raised my rank by 20,000.
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Hey, Himiko...
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
What's this Sakamoto guy like?
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
Girls Only
Cosplay Photo Booth Floor
Bring your own clothes
Dressing room this way
I haven't met him in real life, but he
seemed sort of like a kind older brother.
Maybe he's cool like that one senior, Yoshioka!
Or he could be an old fat guy.
Dream a little.
It's better not to expect too much.
Pictures come out here
Okay, I'm taking the shot!
Three, two, one!
Our First Cosplay
Himiko, why don't you send this photo to that Sakamoto guy?
I'd rather not.
I bet he'd be surprised.
You're actually a busty, blonde high school girl.
You sound like an old man, Miho!
Other than being a foreigner, I was nothing special.
Just a normal high school girl.
I'd go to school and hang out with friends.
Sometimes, I'd play online games.
I really was just a normal girl...
The Bloodstained
High School Girl
until that incident happened.
The Bloodstained
High School Girl
So, this is...
supposed to be my punishment?
Why?
Why is this only happening to me?
Are these all bombs?
Am I really supposed to kill people with these?
There's nothing here.
No one here.
Should I head into the jungle?
It's cold.
I bet there are bugs and snakes!
I can't go in there. My clothes will get dirty!
It's hot.
Where is this island?
I wish I had some sunscreen.
Will I...
ever be able to go back?
Hey, look at this.
I got it yesterday!
Let me see.
"Is there anyone around that you'd like to be rid of?"
What is this?
Some new kind of chain letter?
You give them a name, and you get 100,000 yen?
Really?
Oh, I've heard of this.
It's led to some crazy incidents lately.
I saw it on the news.
They're saying that people have actually gone missing.
So, it's for real?
Then let's name someone whose death wouldn't bother us and get ourselves 100,000 yen!
That's awful, Arisa.
You suck.
Hey... Hey!
Oh, you're awake?
H-Hang on.
Calm down.
I'm not going to hurt you.
Believe me, we aren't your enemies.
They're all...
men.
But there's no telling when someone might show up who doesn't feel that way.
Would you come with us?
Well...
This is a big island.
I had a look from a cliff, and I didn't see signs of anyone living here.
No nearby islands, either.
We'll have to wait for a passing ship.
Then we're stuck here?
There's no guarantee we can get back.
We might have to do as we're told and play this game.
Right now, we all need to work together!
Don't say weird stuff like that.
Don't even joke about it.
It's too hot for this.
Shut up, hypocrite.
What do you mean by hypocrite?
I'm a teacher.
I intend to do what's right, regardless of the situation.
I don't know about that.
People like that are always the most powerless.
Powerless?!
I'm a 4th dan in judo.
Don't underestimate me.
Judo?
There are no floor mats here.
And you think judo will help you against one of these?
D-Don't be stupid.
You reached for a bomb.
That mean you're ready to fight, huh?
Let's see how long your ideals will last.
Will you still use that bomb?
Or will you keep doing the right thing and let me kill you?
However...
If you kill us to save your own life,
you're just a hypocrite.
Well?
Don't you want to kill us both now?
Talking about what's "right", is only hypocrisy here.
L-Let me go.
Whoops.
Oh, well.
I give up.
It was just a joke. A joke.
If I were going to kill you, I would've long ago.
Just stop it!
Didn't we group up because we intended to work together?
Everyone's going nuts because
we have these weapons.
Let's all put our weapons in one place.
We'll pick a leader to watch over them.
If we all pick the leader, we won't have to worry, right?
And how do we know that leader won't get any strange ideas?
That's right.
Who'd be the leader?
I think she would be a good choice.
Me?
I get it. Good idea.
I'll have faith in her as our leader.
This thing's heavy.
I'm glad to be rid of it.
Now you, too.
Your stun gun, as well.
I'm the leader?
Because I'm weak?
Because I'm a woman?
But leaving me in charge can't...
What?
Hey, look.
It dropped something.
Let's go.
I want to see what that was.
Oh, wow.
Awesome!
Good food, drinks, body soap, and even sunscreen.
Sunscreen? Where?
Hey, can we eat some?
If we don't, this stuff will spoil fast.
Eat up.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Where did the food come from?
Look at how much you're eating.
Food's valuable here.
Shouldn't we divide it fairly and eat it little by little?
You just chowed down without a thought.
You should be ashamed!
And in the first place...
Shut up.
Now we'll have some quiet.
I'm so happy!
We get to hang out at my beloved Yoshioka's!
You're obsessed with him, aren't you?
It was so nice of you to invite me.
He lives in the same building as I do.
I said a friend wanted to meet him,
so he said to bring them over.
He also said that the other band members would be coming.
Really?!
Judgment Flash is gonna be there?
They're already here.
It's him! It's really him!
It's like a dream.
I'm going to stop by my place.
My beloved Yoshioka, right before me!
You guys go on ahead.
Hello there, Yoshioka.
Welcome, mademoiselle.
Hey, wake up!
Hey!
Be quiet.
He's still asleep.
This is our only chance to run.
Run?
Have you forgotten what happened yesterday?
If we stay with him, we'll be next.
Let's hurry.
We'll take all the food and BIMs while we've got the chance.
Just... a minute.
Sorry.
We've been walking quite a while, haven't we?
Are you okay?
I just need to rest a little.
I'll be fine.
Let's have a drink.
Th-Thanks.
Y-You're nice, aren't you?
I definitely felt something.
It's him.
He's following us.
Let's hurry!
Run!
How can you tell?
This seems to have turned into a radar.
No way.
Believe me.
I just moved my fingers a little and...
There he is.
I moved my fingers, and I really saw him.
How?
I don't know!
For now, just run!
If he catches us, he'll kill us!
A rope bridge?
H-Hurry!
I weigh too much.
I'd fall right through!
Let's take another path.
But there aren't any others.
What do you think you're doing?
He's here!
You knew I was following you.
How?
How? With the radar.
Radar?
What did you say?
He doesn't know about it?
Th-Then...
He followed us without using his radar?!
What are you talking about?
If you won't give that back to me, I'll take it back.
S-Stay away!
A bomb?
That was a bomb?
It wasn't like mine.
I made it.
Everyone has different types.
The plants are all dying.
Some type of defoliant?
This is bad.
I can't believe he tracked us through the jungle.
From now on, let's stick to the rocks.
Y-You're right.
Why won't he let go of me?
There are plenty of other enemies.
Let's look for a hiding place where we can set an ambush
and prepare for the next fight.
Fight?
That's right! We have to fight!
If we hesitate for even a moment, we'll be killed!
So, you're telling me to kill someone?
You saw what he did!
It's kill or be killed.
You have to kill to protect yourself.
No! I don't want to kill anyone.
Please, unhand me!
Why won't you?! You'll be killed!
Or will you stay on this island forever?
I said, let go of me!
Listen, Himiko.
Stay quiet.
No!
You...
What the hell was that for?!
That hurt, you know?
Mom was always better at hitting me.
Get off me!
Why are you running?
Because I'm fat and creepy?
Because I'm sweaty and stinky?
It's okay.
I took a shower the day before yesterday.
Stop it.
I'll protect you.
No!
You're late, Himiko.
I'm sorry, Yoshioka.
I was getting some snacks.
Come in.
Excuse me!
Oh, she's here...
the one we really wanted, Himiko.
Arisa...
Yuki?
Hey...
Listen, Himiko.
Stay quiet.
I'll show you a good time.
N-No!
Yoshioka!
Miho!
Himiko!
Shut up, damn it!
H-Himiko...
Miho!
Himiko, you bitch.
Himiko...
Come on!
Himiko!
I've gotta call the cops.
Call Mom!
I brought everyone over to
Yoshioka's and only I escaped.
The case got a lot of publicity.
Yoshioka and his band were arrested.
And my friends all moved away.
And then...
I hate you.
I hate you!
I hope you disappear!
So, this is... supposed to be my punishment?
Is that it, Miho?
Rain?
Found you!
That hurt!
Just wait, and I'll punish you.
Punish me?
This...
I know how to use it now.
Seems that when you use the radar, others can see your position.
But depending on how you use it, you can also tell where someone is.
That's how I was able to find you again.
Now... How shall I punish you?
Get off of me!
You're heavy!
T-Titties!
Someone...
Someone save me!
Nobody's coming.
Because I ran.
Because I betrayed them.
Oh? You aren't going to resist anymore?
I guess that means it's okay, right?
The last girl I liked acted that way.
If they don't resist at all, that means it's okay, right?
But it's not fair...
After I was done, everyone got mad at me.
Now, then.
Let's punish...
this naughty girl!
Mom...
I'm sorry.
Wh-Wh-What's that?!
I'd rather die...
than let him rape me.
We'll die together!
Save me!
He's running?
I'm going to die alone?
Coward!
I killed someone,
but I don't feel guilty.
Instead, I'm proud that I protected myself.
I won't hesitate anymore.
Men are scum.
All the men on this island are my enemies.
They're scum.
I hold my breath and close my eyes
iki wo sezu me wo fuseta
The sky is glittering so brightly
hikyou na hodo kirameku aozora ga
Coloring the space over our heads
kono machi no zujou wo color
I can't stop shedding tears
tomedonaku namida furaseru kara
I can't just push it aside as memories
omoide ni wa dekinai
Just seeing you made me so happy
au dake de ureshikatta
I didn't understand you
kimi no koto shirazu ni
And hurt you
kizutsukete
Nobody knows
nobody knows
You don't have to give me another chance
gomen ne watashi wo mou
Just forget about me
yurusanaide wasurete
I ran after the girl,
but I found some guy instead.
He told me a terrifying story,
about why my memory had vanished
and about the whole system that's behind BTOOOM!.
Episode
Survival